CJ.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Hey, this is Lesne, Los Angeles Rams.
>> What's going on, Lesne?
>> Hey, man. We're gonna We're We just
traded up to pick 197.
We're a little earlier than the
television, but we're going to draft. We
do 197 picks.
>> Come on, coach. What took you so long?
>> Oh, man. It took us 196 picks, but we
finally got here. I'm going to put you
on the phone when you do that, coach.
Show them that
>> CJ
going on. Congrats, man. How we doing?
>> Doing great.
>> Hey, we're fired up, man. I love love
love your body of work. Love your tape,
man. Love love everything that we've
heard about you and can't wait to get to
work with you, man. It's going to be a
lot of fun.
>> Can't wait. I can't wait, coach. I
really appreciate it.
>> Oh, man. That's awesome. I'm going to
put you on the phone with your new OC,
Nate Shield House. But we're excited,
man. I can't wait to get to get you
going and it's going to be a lot of fun.
>> That's awesome, man. Here's here's my
Here's Nate Shield House. Awesome.
>> CJ, what's going on, man? How are you?
>> What's going on? I'm good.
>> Family fired up.
>> Yes, sir.
>> It's going to be a hell of a celebration
tonight, man.
>> Yes, sir.
>> We're uh we're fired up to have you
here, man. Being a part of something
special, man. Special special group on
the offic.
So, we're excited, man. Excited to get
you out here. Uh get you going, man.
You enjoy this moment, man. Enjoy the
night.
>> We'll see you soon, man.
>> Thank you.